Wellness, meditation and personal development.

    Search  Search …

Wellness, meditation and personal development.

    Search  Search …
    
    * Search  Search …
        
* Menu

[Home](https://yunibalance.com/) » Privacy Statement

Privacy Statement
=================

_This privacy statement was last updated on November 5, 2023 and applies to citizens and legal permanent residents of the European Economic Area and Switzerland._  

In this privacy statement, we explain what we do with the data we obtain about you via [https://yunibalance.com](https://yunibalance.com/). We recommend you carefully read this statement. In our processing we comply with the requirements of privacy legislation. That means, among other things, that:

* we clearly state the purposes for which we process personal data. We do this by means of this privacy statement;
* we aim to limit our collection of personal data to only the personal data required for legitimate purposes;
* we first request your explicit consent to process your personal data in cases requiring your consent;
* we take appropriate security measures to protect your personal data and also require this from parties that process personal data on our behalf;
* we respect your right to access your personal data or have it corrected or deleted, at your request.

If you have any questions, or want to know exactly what data we keep of you, please contact us.

1\. Purpose, data and retention period
--------------------------------------

We may collect or receive personal information for a number of purposes connected with our business operations which may include the following: (click to expand)

### 1.1 Contact - Through phone, mail, email and/or webforms

For this purpose we use the following data:

* A first and last name
* An email address
* A telephone number

The basis on which we may process these data is:

Retention period

We retain this data until the service is terminated.

### 1.2 Compiling and analyzing statistics for website improvement.

For this purpose we use the following data:

* Internet activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer's interaction with an Internet Web site, application, or advertisement

The basis on which we may process these data is:

Retention period

We retain this data until the service is terminated.

2\. Cookies
-----------

Our website uses cookies. For more information about cookies, please refer to our [Cookie Policy](https://yunibalance.com/cookie-policy/). 

3\. Disclosure practices
------------------------

We disclose personal information if we are required by law or by a court order, in response to a law enforcement agency, to the extent permitted under other provisions of law, to provide information, or for an investigation on a matter related to public safety.

If our website or organisation is taken over, sold, or involved in a merger or acquisition, your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers and will be passed on to the new owners.

4\. Security
------------

We are committed to the security of personal data. We take appropriate security measures to limit abuse of and unauthorised access to personal data. This ensures that only the necessary persons have access to your data, that access to the data is protected, and that our security measures are regularly reviewed.

5\. Third-party websites
------------------------

This privacy statement does not apply to third-party websites connected by links on our website. We cannot guarantee that these third parties handle your personal data in a reliable or secure manner. We recommend you read the privacy statements of these websites prior to making use of these websites.

6\. Amendments to this privacy statement
----------------------------------------

We reserve the right to make amendments to this privacy statement. It is recommended that you consult this privacy statement regularly in order to be aware of any changes. In addition, we will actively inform you wherever possible.

7\. Accessing and modifying your data
-------------------------------------

If you have any questions or want to know which personal data we have about you, please contact us. You can contact us by using the information below. You have the following rights:

* You have the right to know why your personal data is needed, what will happen to it, and how long it will be retained for.
* Right of access: You have the right to access your personal data that is known to us.
* Right to rectification: you have the right to supplement, correct, have deleted or blocked your personal data whenever you wish.
* If you give us your consent to process your data, you have the right to revoke that consent and to have your personal data deleted.
* Right to transfer your data: you have the right to request all your personal data from the controller and transfer it in its entirety to another controller.
* Right to object: you may object to the processing of your data. We comply with this, unless there are justified grounds for processing.

Please make sure to always clearly state who you are, so that we can be certain that we do not modify or delete any data of the wrong person.

8\. Submitting a complaint
--------------------------

If you are not satisfied with the way in which we handle (a complaint about) the processing of your personal data, you have the right to submit a complaint to the Data Protection Authority.

9\. Contact details
-------------------

Yunibalance  
Hårdvallsgatan 18, 115 46 Stockholm  
Sweden  
Website: [https://yunibalance.com](https://yunibalance.com/)  
Email: privacy@yunibalance.com  
Phone number: +46704698754

##### Recent Posts

##### Privacy Menu

Copyright © 2024 [Yunibalance](https://yunibalance.com/ "Yunibalance") – All rights reserved

Manage Cookie Consent

To provide the best experiences, we use technologies like cookies to store and/or access device information. Consenting to these technologies will allow us to process data such as browsing behavior or unique IDs on this site. Not consenting or withdrawing consent, may adversely affect certain features and functions.

Functional  Functional Always active

The technical storage or access is strictly necessary for the legitimate purpose of enabling the use of a specific service explicitly requested by the subscriber or user, or for the sole purpose of carrying out the transmission of a communication over an electronic communications network.

Preferences  Preferences

The technical storage or access is necessary for the legitimate purpose of storing preferences that are not requested by the subscriber or user.

Statistics  Statistics

The technical storage or access that is used exclusively for statistical purposes. The technical storage or access that is used exclusively for anonymous statistical purposes. Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider, or additional records from a third party, information stored or retrieved for this purpose alone cannot usually be used to identify you.

Marketing  Marketing

The technical storage or access is required to create user profiles to send advertising, or to track the user on a website or across several websites for similar marketing purposes.

Accept Deny View preferences Save preferences [View preferences](#)

Manage consent
